my solution for this problem has an easy concept 

to get the maximum area you need maximum width and maximum height

to get maximum width you need to set a pointer at the beginning and a pointer at the end.

what about the maximum height?

    the pointers will not move until we check which of the heights is small, the pointer that contain the small height will move.
    
    this will reduce the width, but in return we are moving to a new height which may be bigger.
