this problem is divided into two parts:
    
    1. calculate the number of nodes in the linked list then you can define the index of the middle element
    2. iterate through the nodes of the linked list until you get the middle element

tip: always set a variable to your "head node" of the linked list, because this is the point you will always need to do whaever the process you want to do, but if you directly deal with the "head node" without first assigned it to another variable, then you list your starting point.
