question will come to your mind when you read the code of the implementation.

why we just stick with the implementation using "python list" ?

the implementation of stack using python list is not efficient interms of memory. if you want to insert an element, and because list is a dynamic array, this will lead to provide slots more than we need because of the nature of the dynamic array.

unlike list in implementation the stack, "deque" class is built on top on doubly linked list, so the problem of memory is solved with this.


so we can say that, "deque" is much efficient to implement stack.
